{
  "openingRemarks": "Do not bother to simplify the result<br>E.g. can enter \\(\\dfrac{250}{100}\\) as \\(2\\frac{50}{100}\\) instead of \\(2\\frac{1}{2}\\)<p>Also enter \"n/a\" for any result which is not defined",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Express \\(1 \\div 2\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "0 1/2"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(11 \\div 4\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "2 3/4"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(7 \\div 2\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "3 1/2"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(14 \\div 3\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "4 2/3"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(1 \\div 0\\) as mixed fraction",
      "answer": "n/a"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(3 \\div 4\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "0 3/4"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(1 \\div 1\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(5 \\div 0\\) as mixed fraction",
      "answer": "n/a"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(4 \\div 1\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(9 \\div 2\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "4 1/2"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(3 \\div 0\\) as mixed fraction",
      "answer": "n/a"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(7 \\div 4\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "1 3/4"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(15 \\div 4\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "3 3/4"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(3 \\div 2\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "1 1/2"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(0 \\div 0\\) as mixed fraction",
      "answer": "n/a"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(9 \\div 5\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "1 4/5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(29 \\div 5\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "5 4/5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(5 \\div 2\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "2 1/2"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(11 \\div 2\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "5 1/2"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(19 \\div 4\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "4 3/4"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(5 \\div 1\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(4 \\div 0\\) as mixed fraction",
      "answer": "n/a"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(4 \\div 5\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "0 4/5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(8 \\div 3\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "2 2/3"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(11 \\div 3\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "3 2/3"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(14 \\div 5\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "2 4/5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(3 \\div 1\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(5 \\div 3\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "1 2/3"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(2 \\div 1\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(17 \\div 3\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "5 2/3"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(24 \\div 5\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "4 4/5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(2 \\div 0\\) as mixed fraction",
      "answer": "n/a"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(19 \\div 5\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "3 4/5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(23 \\div 4\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "5 3/4"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(2 \\div 3\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "0 2/3"
    },
    {
      "question": "Express \\(0 \\div 1\\) as mixed fraction",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "answer": "0"
    }
  ]
}
